Delia Rauftlin

Hackney, London

Mobile: 07340 221889 Email: delia.r@windowslive.com

Portfolio

Personal Profile

Over the past 5 years, my journey in the Hospitality sector has been an enriching experience. Starting as Bar Staff and steadily progressing to the role of Bar Assistant Manager, I've acquired invaluable skills in communication, problem-solving, and teamwork, which have made me adaptable and resourceful. Along the way, I've also discovered that I possess a strong work ethic, attention to detail, and a reliable nature.

Last year, I decided to take a step back from management to focus on my personal growth and future aspirations. While exploring new possibilities, I enrolled in an online course on the fundamentals of Web Development, which ignited a keen interest in this field.

I have since completed an intensive bootcamp, where I acquired a strong grasp of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, GitHub, SQL, and Python. Eager to further refine and expand my skillset, I'm committed to continuous learning and dedicated to excelling in this dynamic industry. My passion for acquiring new knowledge drives me to embrace every opportunity for growth.

Education and IT Training

May 2023 – Aug 2023 Just IT Training Ltd, London

Digital Skills Bootcamp: Software Development

A twelve week intensive bootcamp covering the fundamentals of Web and Software development focusing on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL

& Python.

Aug 2011 – Jul 2014 WKS KV Bern, Switzerland

Commercial Employee, Federal Diploma of Vocational Education &

Training (Comparable to Level 3 Apprenticeship in the UK)

Grades (6,0 constitutes English (5,8), French (5,5), Business & Economics (4,7),

the best possible) Information & Communication (4,8)

IT Skills

Software Development Skills: Python, MySQL

Web Technology: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Core Programming Languages: JavaScript, Python

Projects:

- Created a website for a restaurant using just HTML and CSS
- Created a to do list with vanilla JavaScript using loops, conditional statements, DOM Manipulation, local storage and more
- Compiled a database for a film library and wrote a program where the end-user can browse through those films and perform actions such as updating and deleting records

Employment History

Sep 2022 – Present Flying Horse, London Bar Staff

Main duties performed:

- Serving customers in a sometimes loud and hectic environment where good communication skills are key to a successful workflow and to securing returning customers
- Maintaining a high level of cleanliness and standards even at peak times

Jun 2022 – Sep 2022 Canada Water Library, London Café Supervisor

Main duties performed:

- Opening, running, and closing the café while being by myself
- Cooking pastry ensuring there would be neither too little nor too much, in order to avoid waste
- Making coffee and serving customers

Sep 2021 – Jun 2022 Belushi's London Bridge, London Bar Trainee Assistant Manager

Main duties performed:

- Running shifts, opening and closing the bar as the duty manager
- Creating seating charts and deciding which sports to show on which TVs to meet demand and guarantee the best possible viewing experience for our customers
- Cash up and Zonal declarations/banking
- Ensuring bar, back bar, and floor areas are tidy and up to standard
- Training new and existing employees
- Hosting and seating customers creating a welcoming environment
- Table service during quieter times as well as for big sporting events, keeping track of open tabs

Sep 2020 – Sep 2021 Belushi's, Bath Bar Supervisor

Main duties performed:

- Running shifts, opening and closing the bar as the duty manager
- Cash up and Zonal declarations/banking
- Ensuring bar, back bar, and floor areas are tidy and up to standard
- Training new and existing employees

Jul 2020 – Sep 2020 Belushi's, Newquay Bar and Floor Staff

Main duties performed:

- Table service for around 50 tables inside and in two separate outside areas during peak season
- Running food/drinks
- Later on I would go on to working behind the bar

Jun 2018– Jul 2020 Flying Horse, London Bar Supervisor

Main duties performed:

- Opening as closing the bar
- Serving customers
- Stock take
- Accepting deliveries
- Inputting invoices
- Performing line cleans

Dec 2017 – Jun 2018 Cuba, Colombia, Ecuador, Peru, Bolivia, Chile Backpacking

 Backpacked through South America by myself with the goal to learn Spanish and to broaden my horizon and do something that I had never done to that extent before

Jul 2015 – Oct 2017 merz+benteli ag, Niederwangen, Switzerland Sales Representative & Receptionist

Main duties performed:

- Processing orders from my assigned customers nationally and internationally; this included entering their orders into software, organising transport through our carrier, and invoicing etc. as well as ensuring smooth flow during customs clearance.
- Answering the main landline telephone
- Amending safety data sheets and technical data sheets in line with REACH compliance
- Maintaining product master data

Aug 2011 – Jul 2014 Marti Holding AG, Moosseedorf, Switzerland Apprentice Commercial Employee

Main objectives:

Insight into different departments where I would switch departments every 3-6 months.
 Departments I worked in include: HR, Accounting, Reception, Marketing, and Project Management

References